# **RAPHAEL**

# **B. RODRIGUES**

raphaelbarbosa.rodrigues@gmail.com

raphael-b-rodrigues-08b02889

(11) 96548-2567

## **SUMMARY**

**Developer** with more than two years of experience, I have already worked in many e-commerce projects using platforms such as VTEX (Certified), Magento and OpenCart using technologies like React, TypeScript, GraphQL and PHP.

At the moment I am in the 5th period of my Computer Science degree and I'm looking for a place where I can work with new technologies and have contact with professionals who I can learn, teach and change the world.

### **EDUCATION**

**Computer Science - UNASP** 

2020 - 2023

**Computer Technician - UNASP** 

2017 - 2019

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**4Vets** - Fullstack Developer

03/2020 - 11/2020

Developing new projects and creating new features in ecommerce platform such as Magento and OpenCart using PHP, also responsible for the configuration and maintenance of Linux servers using Docker containers, and AWS services like Route53 and EC2, and also extracting data from relational databases to report generation.

#### **Enext -** Front-end Developer

09/2020 - 08/2021

Working with the development, maintenance and implementation of front-end projects using Javascript and related technologies in the ecommerce platform VTEX, building responsive landing pages, managing internal and external scripts with GTM, being and also responsible for managing the squad backlog and to support its members.

#### **Corebiz -** Front-end Developer

08/2020 - at moment

Working in dedicated squads with the development and maintenance of VTEX ecommerces using technologies from Javascript ecosystem, such as React, TypeScript and GraphQL.

# **TECH SKILLS**

### **Front-end**

React, Redux, Styled-Components, ES6, SCSS, HTML, CSS e JQuery.

### **Back-end**

PHP, MySQL e Node.JS.

### **Ferramentas e Sistemas**

Linux, Git, NPM, TypeScript, GraphQL

### Conhecimento em

Java, C, C#, AWS, Docker, Nginx, SQL Server, MongoDB e Bootstrap, Webpack, Jest.

# **LANGUAGES**

Inglês - Intermediary CNA (2017 - 2021)

Português - Nativo

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

**VTEX -** IO Developer 12/2021 - 12/2023